<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="../assets/xml/rss.xsl" media="all"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Circuit Lover's Space (Posts about loki)</title><link>https://circuitlover.github.io/</link><description></description><atom:link href="https://circuitlover.github.io/categories/loki.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><language>en</language><copyright>Contents © 2021 &lt;a href="mailto:circuitlover1142@gmail.com"&gt;Circuit Lover&lt;/a&gt; 
&lt;a rel="license" href="https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-sa/4.0/"&gt;
&lt;img alt="Creative Commons License BY-NC-SA"
style="border-width:0; margin-bottom:12px;"
src="https://i.creativecommons.org/l/by-nc-sa/4.0/88x31.png"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;</copyright><lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Jul 2021 13:56:33 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>Nikola (getnikola.com)</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>What drives you in life ?</title><link>https://circuitlover.github.io/posts/what-drives-you-in-life/</link><dc:creator>Circuit Lover</dc:creator><description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is my first blog post.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Disclaimer: May be I'm not a good writer, but I try to be :-)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For this post, what drives me ;-) is &lt;a href="https://janusworx.com/blog/thoughts-on-setting-up-a-blog/" title="jasonbraganza's article about how to set up a blog"&gt;jasonbraganza's article about how to set up a blog&lt;/a&gt; and a scene from Loki's fifth episode. you can find below the images of the scene.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://0x0.st/-Vpk.png" title="Renslayer asks hunter B-15 about what drives sylvie"&gt;&lt;img alt="Renslayer asks hunter B-15 about what drives sylvie" src="https://0x0.st/-Vpk.png" title="Renslayer asks hunter B-15 about what drives sylvie"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the above scene, you can see the character Judge Renslayer asks Hunter B-15 about Sylvie (a fugitive variant of loki),  that is &lt;strong&gt;what drives her.&lt;/strong&gt; Then, Hunter B-15 adds a fitting answer to it, as below &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://0x0.st/-Vpd.png" title="Hunter B-15 Answers to Renslayer"&gt;&lt;img alt="Hunter B-15 Answers to Renslayer" src="https://0x0.st/-Vpd.png" title="Hunter B-15 Answers to Renslayer"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yes, &lt;strong&gt;revenge drives sylvie.&lt;/strong&gt; According to the Loki Series, Sylvie is a fugitive variant of Loki. Because, the &lt;strong&gt;Time Variance Authority (TVA)&lt;/strong&gt;, which controls time, ruined sylvie's life by capturing her at young age from her timeline. So there is no life for her. But, however she managed to escape and hide from the hands of TVA by jumping from one timeline to another. The characterization of sylvie is like that she never bows down, but feed her vengeance with the aim to kill the head of TVA.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After I've seen this scene,  a question strikes me hard is that, what drives us in our life. Something like we need a driving factor, to create or do something. The driving factor may be anything like end result of what you gonna do; your anger to prove yourself; your own personal experiences; your interest; a social cause; or even money you will get for that thing. So, something we need that drives us, whether to do good or bad things.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The robustness of your driving point depends on many factors like yourself; the end result; or the cause, for what you're doing etc,. For a good deed, the driving factor is much stonger. If the cause is good in general like a social cause, then your driving factor is way much stronger than anything like you'll overcome any hurdles that impedes your way. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;People who are doing bad deeds may have stronger driving point, but their end result will be in vain only. Because their base is wrong, they do it on behalf of bad motives.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finally, think yourself that what drives you; or motivates you in every moment. And make sure the driving factor for you is realy strong with the good cause.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Do good; Be good; Spread love &amp;lt;3&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><category>general</category><category>loki</category><category>marvel</category><category>personal thoughts</category><category>sylvie</category><guid>https://circuitlover.github.io/posts/what-drives-you-in-life/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jul 2021 13:29:10 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>